[{"answer": "You my friend", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend around", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "It's your radiator hose.  It's busted", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Well, you know so much why don't you just fix it yourself", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Somewhere else?  Mister, somewhere else is fifty miles from here. Only other gas station down in town closed 3 years ago when the mine got shut..", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yeah, I can fix it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Gotta run over to the yard and see if I can find a hose like this one, or close enough. Gonna take time", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Time", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "How much time", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " What time is it now", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yeah I want something.  I want you to run over to that machine and get me a pop", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Hell no, I can't do that myself.  I'm blind.  Can't you see that", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You can't do that yourself", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'm sorry, I didn'", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, I didn'", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't know.  I thought you were keeping the sun out of your eyes", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Do you have to call me that", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Maybe I don't want you to", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You don't have that dead look in your eyes like the only thing you live for is to get through the day", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Drove into Superior?  What for", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What happens when you lose", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Somewhere else.  I've never been anywhere else.  Just once.  Years ago.  Went to the State Fair. It was nice, but it wasn't nothing", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "That's good.  Cools you right off.  I saw you watching me", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I didn't say it bothered me", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I'm sorry.  I didn't mean to", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Did you like i", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Like they're made of polyester", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Nothing like a little liveliness", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Who the hell are you", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Husband ...", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You can't just walk in here and walk out, you sonufabitch! I'm gonna tear you a new asshole", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "It ain't broke", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I guess we've never been introduced proper. my friend", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I'm a solid man", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "That's all right. He doesn't want to give me the bag..", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You ain't got no credit card but you got a lawyer. Sweet talk me all you want.  Didn't you read the sign? It says..", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I want my hundred and fort", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Genuine Draft", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I'll fuckin' take it. To go", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I wasn't doing anything", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Make time?  Is everybody in this town on drugs", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What was that all about", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "More like my friend is after every man she sees", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "that place. Fucking deadbeat. We head about you. You owe", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "my friend who?", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Right, Mr. my friend. And that's not the half of it. I got your money, and I go into this little grocery store in this hicktown to get something to eat and then... well, it gets ", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "No. Two of them. Two robbers. And they get nailed... get shot by the old lady", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I was hoping we could talk", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "About things.  About your wife", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "You drive a hard bargain, but I had a feeling you were my boy when I met you", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Don't say that.  I had a marriage of convenience with my friend, and look where that's lead...  Well, looks like we got ourselves a contract", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "How do you want it", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "You want to do this yourself?  I don't have to do this, you know", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Are there snakes out here", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Doesn't the isolation bother you", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Oh yeah. It's far, it's another world", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": " I wish I could", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Honey, baby, I . I can't even get out of here . Believe it or not, I need a lousy hundred and fifty bucks to get my car back from that crazy mechanic..", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "I hate to bust your bubble honey, but I wasn't defending you", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "I wasn't going to fight for you.  I was just going to beat the shit out of your boyfriend", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "How old are you", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "No, I don't want to take you for a ride. What I want is for ... Hey, you don't think you can get", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "You said this morning the hose was going to run me on", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "It's going to cost you tw", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Yep.  For the hose.  But while you was gone I replaced a gasket.  That's going to run you another fifty", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "How much", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "One way", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Get up, Mister!  Don't ever let it be said my friend beat the living shit out of someone without giving them a fair chance", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "I'm doing what any man would do if he'd been offended.  I'm stompin' your ass", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Because I know you're full of shit", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": " I thought you couldn't get your car", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "You got my pity", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Oh, she was worth it.  She was worth every black minute since", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": " Awright, let's go. I want to be fifty miles from here before the sun comes up", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": " Funny thing... I'll get the bags", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Let it go, baby. It's the past. I got a past..", "docId": "u-turn_shooting.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": " What do you want me to say", "qsentId": 80}]